{"data":[{"question":"Carbohydrates and fats are two essential sources of energy for animal grow.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"and fats","b":"sources","c":"for","d":"grow","answer":"4","explain":" -Grow-> growth","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"By passing sunlight through a prism, the light is separate into a spectrum of colors.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"By passing","b":"through","c":"is separate","d":"spectrum of","answer":"3","explain":" - Is separate-> is separated","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"In spite modern medical technology, many diseases caused by viruses are still not curable.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In spite","b":"many","c":"by viruses","d":"not","answer":"1","explain":" - In spite-> in spite of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Though Pablo Picasso was primarily a painting, he also became a fine sculptor, engraver, and ceramist.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Though","b":"primarily","c":"painting","d":"fine","answer":"3","explain":" - Painting-> painter","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"People who live in small towns often seem more warm and friendly than people who live in populated densely areas.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"small towns","b":"seem","c":"who","d":"populated densely","answer":"4","explain":" - Populated densely-> densely populated","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"It took eight years to complete the Erie Canal, the 365-mile waterway which it connects Albany and Buffalo in New York State.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"It","b":"to complete","c":"the 365-mile","d":"which it connects","answer":"4","explain":" - Which it connects-> which connects","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Every candidate under considering for a federal job must undergo a thorough medical examination.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"under","b":"considering","c":"undergo","d":"medical","answer":"2","explain":" - Considering-> consideration","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The masterpiece A Christmas Carol wrote by Charles Dickens in 1843.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"wrote","c":"by","d":"in","answer":"2","explain":" \n- Wrote-> written","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Species like snakes, lizards, coyotes, squirrels, and jack rabbits seems to exist quite happily in the desert.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"like","b":"seems to","c":"quite happily","d":"the","answer":"2","explain":" - Seems-> seem","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The disposable camera, a single-use camera preloaded with print film, has appeared in the late 1980s, and has become very popular.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"a","b":"preloaded with","c":"has appeared","d":"has become","answer":"3","explain":" - Had appeared-> appeared","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"}]}